<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English on Code996</title>
    <link>https://www.code996.cn/categories/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English on Code996</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.code996.cn/categories/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-1</title>
      <link>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-1/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
Unit 1 Growing Up Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Do you know who John Lennon was? 2. Have you ever heard the song before? 3. What does Lennon think of growing up? Is it easy or full of adventures? 4. Can you guess what the texts in this unit are going to be about?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-2</title>
      <link>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-2/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
Unit 2 Friendship Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Have you ever heard of Dionne Warwick? Have you happened to hear her sing? 2. What does a fair weather friend mean? 3. What does Dionne Warwick think friends are for? 4. Does the song give you any idea of what the stories in this unit will be about?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-3</title>
      <link>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-3/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
Unit 3 Understanding Science Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Who is it about? 2. What questions interest him? 3. What makes his achievements so remarkable? Part II Text A Professor Hawking thinks it important to keep everybody in touch with what science is about. In this article he explains why.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-4</title>
      <link>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-4/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
Unit 4 American Dream Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. According to Dr. Hertz, what did the American Dream mean to his grandparents? 2. In Dr. Hertz&#39;s opinion, who wants people to believe in the American Dream? Why? 3. Why does Dr. Hertz say the American Dream is in one&#39;s head and in one&#39;s pocket?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-5</title>
      <link>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-5/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
Unit 5 Romance Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Do you have a favorite love song? What is its name? Who is the singer? Can you sing or hum the tune? 2. What is the song you have just heard mainly about? 3. Do you think it appropriate to begin this unit with a love song?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-6</title>
      <link>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-6/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
Unit 6 Animal Intelligence Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. What do you know about Michael Jackson? 2. How does he feel about Ben? Why? 3. Do you think the song Ben reveals something about the relationship between man and animals? If so, what is it? 4. Is the song related to the theme of the unit animal intelligence?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-7</title>
      <link>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-7/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
Unit 7 Emergency Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. How did the father understand courage at first? 2. What did courage mean to the father after the fire was put out? 3. The poet says that firemen fight a war they can never win. What does he mean?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-8</title>
      <link>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.code996.cn/post/english/1-8/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
Unit 8 Coping with an Educational Problem Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. What was the teacher&#39;s purpose in asking his class the riddle? 2. What can you learn about Little Geoffrey from his answer to the riddle? Was he used to trying to think clearly? Had he formed the habit of making good use of his brain?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>