<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>英语 on 计算机与软件技术公开课</title>
    <link>https://luangeng.space/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 英语 on 计算机与软件技术公开课</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2018. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://luangeng.space/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-1</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-1/</guid>
      <description>Unit 1 Growing Up Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Do you know who John Lennon was? 2. Have you ever heard the song before? 3. What does Lennon think of growing up? Is it easy or full of adventures? 4. Can you guess what the texts in this unit are going to be about? Part</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-2</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-2/</guid>
      <description>Unit 2 Friendship Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Have you ever heard of Dionne Warwick? Have you happened to hear her sing? 2. What does a fair weather friend mean? 3. What does Dionne Warwick think friends are for? 4. Does the song give you any idea of what the stories in this unit will</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-3</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-3/</guid>
      <description>Unit 3 Understanding Science Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Who is it about? 2. What questions interest him? 3. What makes his achievements so remarkable? Part II Text A Professor Hawking thinks it important to keep everybody in touch with what science is about. In this article he explains why. PUBLIC ATTITUDES TOWARD SCIENCE Whether</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-4</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-4/</guid>
      <description>Unit 4 American Dream Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. According to Dr. Hertz, what did the American Dream mean to his grandparents? 2. In Dr. Hertz&#39;s opinion, who wants people to believe in the American Dream? Why? 3. Why does Dr. Hertz say the American Dream is in one&#39;s head and in one&#39;s pocket? 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-5</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-5/</guid>
      <description>Unit 5 Romance Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Do you have a favorite love song? What is its name? Who is the singer? Can you sing or hum the tune? 2. What is the song you have just heard mainly about? 3. Do you think it appropriate to begin this unit with a love song?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-6</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-6/</guid>
      <description>Unit 6 Animal Intelligence Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. What do you know about Michael Jackson? 2. How does he feel about Ben? Why? 3. Do you think the song Ben reveals something about the relationship between man and animals? If so, what is it? 4. Is the song related to the theme of the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-7</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-7/</guid>
      <description>Unit 7 Emergency Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. How did the father understand courage at first? 2. What did courage mean to the father after the fire was put out? 3. The poet says that firemen fight a war they can never win. What does he mean? 4. How does courage as described in the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程1-8</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/1-8/</guid>
      <description>Unit 8 Coping with an Educational Problem Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. What was the teacher&#39;s purpose in asking his class the riddle? 2. What can you learn about Little Geoffrey from his answer to the riddle? Was he used to trying to think clearly? Had he formed the habit of making good use of</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程2-1</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-1/</guid>
      <description>UNIT 1 Ways of Learning Part I Pre-Reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Who should teach whom? Is learning a one-way street? 2. Should we share our dreams for a better life with our parents or keep them to ourselves? 3. Can children ever understand their parents completely? 4. From the song can you guess what the theme</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程2-2</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-2/</guid>
      <description>Unit 2 Text A The Richest Man In America, Down Home Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Who is it about? 2. What happened to him one day? 3. Do you think it was worthwhile to walk two or three miles to pay back the six and a quarter cents? 4. Is the story related to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程2-3</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-3/</guid>
      <description>Unit 2 Text A Father knows Better Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. What sort of a song is it? 2. Who should be sitting up and taking notice? Why? 3. What does the singer think of his parent&#39;s way of doing things? 4. Do you agree with what he says? Part II Text A This</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程2-4</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-4/</guid>
      <description>Unit 4 Text A A Virtual Life Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Is the hero a student or an employee? 2. What was he doing when the boss came in? 3. How did he act in front of his boss? 4. Can you guess what the texts in this unit are going to be about?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程2-5</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-5/</guid>
      <description>Unit 5 Text A True Height Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. What happened to the singer? 2. What helped her pull through all the hardships she suffered? 3. What is the tone of the song? 4. Is the song related to the theme of the unit overcoming obstacles? Part II Text A Look at the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程2-6</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-6/</guid>
      <description>Unit 6 Text A I&#39;m Going To Buy The Brooklyn Bridge Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. Why can&#39;t women be ignored? 2. What price have women had to pay for their wisdom? 3. What happens to them if you try to break their will? 4. Have women realized their dreams? Part II Text A How</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程2-7</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-7/</guid>
      <description>Unit 7 Text A The Glorious Messiness Of English Text Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. What is the passage about? 2. What&#39;s your impression of the English language? 3. Can you give one or two examples to illustrate the messiness of the English language? 4. Can you guess what the texts in this unit are</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程2-8</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/2-8/</guid>
      <description>Unit 8 Text A Saving Nature, But Only For Man Part I Pre-reading Task Listen to the recording two or three times and then think over the following questions: 1. What kind of paradise is described in the song? 2. Why do people have to pay to see the trees? 3. What would happen if farmers continued to use DDT? 4. What is the theme of the song? Part II</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程3-1</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-1/</guid>
      <description>The song you are about to hear is all about taking a break from city life, escaping from the crowds, finding a quiet place, far from the human race. For those of us who live in cities, getting out in the country can provide a welcome break, letting us recharge our batteries2. Out in the country, as the song says, we can find a place to stand alone and take</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程3-2</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-2/</guid>
      <description>The song you are going to listen to is called Abraham, Martin &amp;amp; John, sung by Dion. Abraham, Martin &amp;amp; John Dion Has anybody here, Seen my old friend Abraham, Can you tell me, where he&#39;s gone, He freed a lotta people, But it seems the good they die young, You know I just looked around, And he&#39;s gone, Has anybody here, Seen my old friend John, Can you tell</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程3-3</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-3/</guid>
      <description>The song you are about to hear is all about a &amp;quot;Saturday Night Special&amp;quot;. Listen and see if you can guess what a Saturday Night Special is. Saturday Night Special Lynyrd Skynyrd Two feets they come a-creepin&#39; Like a black cat do. Two bodies a-laying restless, Creeper thinks he&#39;s got nothing to lose. So he creeps into the house, yea, Unlocks the door, And as the man&#39;s reachin&#39; for his</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程3-4</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-4/</guid>
      <description>Every child likes listening to stories. Zoe, a girl with wings, is no exception. Listen carefully and see what story her father is going to tell her. &amp;quot;Now, Zoe, stop fluttering around, and I will tell you a story.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;A true story, papa?&amp;quot; &amp;quot;It all happened exactly as I&#39;m going to tell you. Two thousand and eleven years ago in 1985, a tribe of beings from the Dog Star invaded</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程3-5</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-5/</guid>
      <description>To begin with, let&#39;s listen to a song called There&#39;s No Place Like Home for the Holidays. There&#39;s No Place Like Home For The Holidays Perry Como Oh, there&#39;s no place like home for the holidays &#39;Cause no matter how far away you roam When you pine for the sunshine of a friendly gaze For the holidays you can&#39;t beat home sweet home I met a man who lives in</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程3-6</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-6/</guid>
      <description>The song you are about to hear was first performed at a concert given to raise money to fight against poverty in Africa. Its message is simple, &amp;quot;There are people dying and it is time to help, to lend a hand. It&#39;s no use pretending that someone somewhere will do it for us. So let&#39;s start giving to those with less than ourselves.&amp;quot; The message is clear. The song sings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程3-7</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-7/</guid>
      <description>The song you are about to hear came about through a chance meeting. The singer, Donna Summer, was having a meal with her manager in an expensive restaurant in the plush Beverly Hills area of Los Angeles. As Donna tells the story: &amp;quot;I went into the ladies, and saw one of the waitresses sleeping on a stool1, absolutely exhausted from lack of sleep,&amp;quot; she says. &amp;quot;I woke the lady up</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程3-8</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/3-8/</guid>
      <description>A Clone of Our Own Will humans be the next clones? The technology still has a long way to go before it&#39;s considered safe to try on humans. But even if it were safe, would it be right? Let&#39;s hear what Professor Hank Greely of Standford University has to say on this topic. Interviewer: When will we clone a human? Greely: That&#39;s not a simple question. I think we have</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程4-1</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-1/</guid>
      <description>They say that pride comes before a fall. In the case of both Napoleon and Hitler, the many victories they enjoyed led them to believe that anything was possible, that nothing could stand in their way. Russia&#39;s icy defender was to prove them wrong. 人道是骄兵必败。就拿拿破仑和希特勒两人来说吧，他们所</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程4-2</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-2/</guid>
      <description>Smart cars that can see, hear, feel, smell, and talk? And drive on their own? This may sound like a dream, but the computer revolution is set to turn it into a reality. 能看、能听、有知觉、具嗅觉、会说话的智能汽车？还能自动驾驶？这听起来或许像</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程4-3</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-3/</guid>
      <description>Harvey Mackay, who runs his own company, often interviews applicants for jobs. Here he lets us into the secret of what qualities an employer is looking for, and gives four tips on what can help you to stand out from the crowd. 自己经营公司的哈维·麦凯经常对求职者进行面试。文中他告诉</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程4-4</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-4/</guid>
      <description>Is America going to decline like other great nations have before? The author thinks not, arguing that the type of society being created in America is quite unlike any that has gone before it. Read what he has to say and see whether you agree. 美国是否会如同历史上其他强国一样走向衰亡？作者持否</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程4-5</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-5/</guid>
      <description>Some people seem easy to understand: their character appears obvious on first meeting. Appearances, however, can be deceptive1. 有些人似乎容易了解:他们的个性在初次交往时就表露无遗。然而，外表可能具有欺骗性。 A Friend in Need Somerset Maugham 1 For thirty years now I</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程4-6</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-6/</guid>
      <description>As the pace of life in today&#39;s world grows ever faster, we seem forever on the go. With so much to do and so little time to do it in, how are we to cope? Richard Tomkins sets about untangling the problem and comes up with an answer. 随着当今世界生活节奏日益加快，我们似乎一直在</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程4-7</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-7/</guid>
      <description>Peggy Noonan lives in New York and writes a weekly column for The Wall Street Journal. This piece is taken from one of them. In it she reflects on her week and on life in the city. Writing less than a year away from the destruction of the World Trade Center, her thoughts are inevitably affected by that terrible event. 佩吉·诺南住在纽约，</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>全新版大学英语综合教程4-8</title>
      <link>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luangeng.space/post/english/4-8/</guid>
      <description>Annie Dillard tells of her visit to the Napo River in the heart of the Ecuadorian jungle, one of nature&#39;s most unspoiled places. She describes the beauty of the forest and her admiration for the people who live there. 安妮·迪拉德讲述了自己游览厄瓜多尔丛林深处的纳波河的经历。那是</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>